necklace4 =[
  {"question":"面容","Answer":"miànróng"},
  {"question":"憔悴不已","Answer":"qiáocuì bùyǐ"},
  {"question":"無奈","Answer":"wúnài"},
  {"question":"依照","Answer":"yīzhào"},
  {"question":"珠寶","Answer":"zhūbǎo"},
  {"question":"珠寶商","Answer":"zhūbǎoshāng"},
  {"question":"珠寶盒","Answer":"zhūbǎo hé"},
  {"question":"地址","Answer":"dìzhǐ"},
  {"question":"老闆","Answer":"lǎobǎn"},
  {"question":"走訪","Answer":"zǒufǎng"},
  {"question":"項鍊","Answer":"xiàngliàn"},
  {"question":"法郎","Answer":"fǎláng"},
  {"question":"目瞪口呆","Answer":"mùdèngkǒudāi"},
  {"question":"立刻","Answer":"lìkè"},
  {"question":"殺價","Answer":"shājià"},
  {"question":"貧窮","Answer":"pínqióng"},
  {"question":"而言","Answer":"éryán"},
  {"question":"丈夫 ","Answer":"zhàngfu  "},
  {"question":"老闆","Answer":"lǎobǎn"},
  {"question":"約","Answer":"yuē"},
  {"question":"取貨","Answer":"qǔhuò"},
  {"question":"欣然","Answer":"xīnrán"},
  {"question":"契約","Answer":"qìyuē"},
  {"question":"繼承","Answer":"jìchéng"},
  {"question":"法郎","Answer":"fǎláng"},
  {"question":"恰好","Answer":"qiàhǎo"},
  {"question":"遺產","Answer":"yíchǎn"},
  {"question":"湊足","Answer":"còuzú"},
  {"question":"剩","Answer":"shèng"},
  {"question":"深表","Answer":"shēnbiǎo"},
  {"question":"遺失","Answer":"yíshī"},
  {"question":"還給","Answer":"huángěi"},
  {"question":"珍","Answer":"zhēn"},
  {"question":"頗有","Answer":"pō yǒu"},
  {"question":"微詞","Answer":"wēicí"},
  {"question":"飽嘗","Answer":"bǎocháng"},
  {"question":"貧窮","Answer":"pínqióng"},
  {"question":"節省開銷","Answer":"jiéshěng kāixiāo"},
  {"question":"辭退","Answer":"cítuì"},
  {"question":"女傭","Answer":"nǚyōng"},
  {"question":"搬進","Answer":"bānjìn"},
  {"question":"租金","Answer":"zūjīn"},
  {"question":"比較","Answer":"bǐjiào"},
  {"question":"便宜","Answer":"piányi"},
  {"question":"閣樓","Answer":"gélóu"},
  {"question":"家務","Answer":"jiāwù"},
  {"question":"清洗","Answer":"qīngxǐ"},
  {"question":"油膩","Answer":"yóunì"},
  {"question":"碗","Answer":"wǎn"},
  {"question":"碟","Answer":"dié"},
  {"question":"骯髒","Answer":"āngzāng"},
  {"question":"直","Answer":"zhí"},
  {"question":"修","Answer":"xiū"},
  {"question":"夫婦","Answer":"fūfù"}
]